Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
Northcutt Ely Papers,
1900-1982
M0223
Ely, Northcutt
ca. 240 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Correspondence, memoranda, research notes, rough drafts of reports, printed reports and pamphlets.
Administrative Information
Access
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Northcutt Ely, 1971, 1973, 1980, 1982, and of his estate, 2002.
Biography
Legal representative of various interests in disputes over water projects on the Colorado and other rivers. Ely was Executive assistant to the Secretary of the Interior during the Hoover Administration.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Correspondence, memoranda, research notes, rough drafts of reports, printed reports and pamphlets.
Collection is organized into four accessions originally treated as separate collections: M0223 (Series 1: Working files; Series 2: General files); M252 (Series 3: Books; Series 4: Magazines; Series 5: Pamphlets; Series 6: Reports; Series 7: Miscellaneous); M269 (Series 8: Oil and Gas; Series 9: Water Irrigation; Series 10: Colorado River), M365, and accession 2002-112.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Colorado River Watershed (Colo.-Mexico); Water conservation -- United States.; Water use -- Taxation -- Law and legislation.; Hoover Dam (Ariz. and Nev.)
Collection Contents
- Series 1. Working files
  - Subseries 1. California Flood Control Project
    - Changes in H. R. 4485 as passed by Senate, effected by conference report, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act F. Y. 1947, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - California Flood Control Project- Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, Pro. to 1947, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, 1949, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, 1950, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - California Flood ControlProject - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, 1951, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, Fy 1951, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, 1953, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, 1954, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - California Flood Control Project - Federal Legislation Appropriations Act, 1955 - 1957, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - California Flood Control Project - State Legislation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - California Flood Control Project - General, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Central Valley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Sacramento (Folsom Table), Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Kaweah (Terminus); C.D. I, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, King's (Pine Flat); H.D. 630 - 631, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Calaveras, Littlejohn; H.D. 545, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Ventura River Basin; H.D. 323, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Santa Ana River Basin, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Los Angeles, Whittier Narrows, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - California Flood Control Project - 'Project Data and Reports, Salinas River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - California Flood Control Project - Project Data and Reports, Arroyo Grande, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - California Flood Control Project - Correspondence State, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - California Flood Control Project - Correspondence Congressional, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - California Flood Control Project - Temporary File, Accession no. M0223 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, other government departments, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, fees and expenses, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Reports on Comprehensive Plans, Federal Report, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Reportson Comprehensive Plans, States Comments, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Subseries 2. California Rivers and Harbors and Miscellaneous Reclamations Projects
    - Authorizations - Napa River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Authorizations - Santa Barbara Reclamation Series 1. Working filesSubseries 2. California Rivers and Harbors and Miscellaneous Reclamations Projects, Accession no. M0223; 32 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      2
    - Authorizations - Solano (Monticello Project), Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence with authority, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Subseries 3. Central Valley Project
    - Correspondence with authority, 1956 - and correspondence with executive officer, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence with authority and executive officer,1953 - 1955, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence with authority and executive officer,1950 - 1952, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence with authority and executive officer,1948 - 1949, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence with authority - Monthly Report, Ely1955 - 1957, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence with authority - Monthly Report, Ely1952 - 1954, Accession no. M0223 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence with authority - Monthly Report, Ely 1945 - 1951, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence with Authority - Reports/agendas, Executive Office, 1948 - 1955, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence with authority - Minutes, meetings with Executive Office, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence with authority - Fees and Expenses, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence with authority - Fees and Expenses, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Correspendence with authority - Budget (State), Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence with authority - Personal Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence with authority - Intra-authority Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence with authority - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memos, 1945 - 1952, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence with authority - Attorney General's Office, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence with authority - Congressional Correspondence, 1953 - 1957, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence with authority - General Correspondence, Central Valley Association, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - General Correspondence, National Reclamation Association, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - General Correspondence, National Rivers and Harbors Congress, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - General Correspondence, California Irrigation District Association, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - General Correspondence, California Farm Bureau Federation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Genral Correspondence, Governor's Water Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Departmental Correspondence, Interior Department, Accession no. M0223 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Departmental Correspondence, War Food Administration, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Departmental Correspondence, War Production Board, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Departmental Correspondence, Federal Power Commission, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Clippings and Releases, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Clippings and Releases, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Maps, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Nevada Power, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: Ickes Program, 1943 - 1945, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      .
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: 1943 - 1945, Program of subsequent reclamation by WFA, 1943, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: P.D. 200 - Friant Kern Canal, Accession no. M0223 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: P.D. 200 - Contra Costa Canal, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: Cost Estimates, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: Authority's Program, 4/18/43, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: Authority's Program, 1945, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Central Valley Project Construction, Interior Department Program: Investigation of Shutdown, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Central Valley Project Construction: War Food Administration Crop Production, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Central Valley Project Construction: Production Board, Stop Orders, 11/42, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Central Valley Project Construction: Production Board, Authority's Correspondence with War Production Board, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Central Valley Project Construction: Production Board, Government Correspondence with White House, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Central Valley Project Construction: Production Board, Contra Costa Canal, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Central Valley Project Construction: Production Board, Construction Materials and Equipment, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - War Manpower Commission, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Resolutions, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Construction, Power Features, Shasta Dam and Power Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Construction, Power Features, Antioch Steam Plant, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Construction, Power Features, Snow Surveys - Water Conditions, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Construction, Rates for Power Features, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Construction, Power Features, Disposal of Power, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Construction, Friant-Kern Canal, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Construction, Tulare Lake - Fresno Slough, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Construction, Project Study Committees, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Construction, Colorado River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Construction., San Diego Water Supply, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Construction, Coachella Valley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Construction, Interior's Post-War Program, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Construction, West Side Projects, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Construction, Construction Status Reports, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Construction, Construction, Repayments, Contracts and Ivanhoe Irrigation District, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Construction, Feather River Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Appropriations, Appropriations,1949, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Appropriations, 1950, Accession no. M0223 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Rivers and Harbors Bill (1944), Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, 1951, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Appropriations, 1952, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Appropriations, 1953, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Appropriations, 1954, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Appropriations, 1955, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Appropriations, Fiscal 1956, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Appropriations, 1957, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Legislation, McCarrow Commission, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Central Valley Soldiers' Settlement Act, Correspondence with Senators, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Central Valley Soldiers' Settlement Act, Memoranda,1944, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Central Valley Soldiers' Settlement Act, Hearings, California, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 110)
      1944
    - Rivers and Harbors Bill (1944), Memoranda, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Rivers and Harbors Bill (1944), Legislative History, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Rivers and Harbors Bill (1944), Making Amendments, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Senate Resolution 295 (1944), Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Senate Resolution 304 (1944), Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Legislation, S. 395 (1945), analyses, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Legislation, S. 395 (1945) (Excess Lands), Memoranda, Legislative History, Drafts, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Legislation, State Legislation, H. J. Res. 139-2-513897 - Water Control, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Legislation, Water Conservation Conference, Chicago Conference, 1944, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Legislation, Water Conservation Conference,' Continuing Committee, 1945, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Legislation, Water Conservation Conference, Mississippi Valley Authority, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Legislation, Water. Conservation Conference, Tennessee Valley Authority Briefs, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Legislation, Water Conservation Conference, Miscellaneous Briefs, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Legislation, Central Valley Authority Bills, Grange Bill, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Legislation, Central Valley Authority Bills, Interior Department Proposals, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Legislation, Central Valley Authority Bills, Rankin Bill, H.R. 1824 (1945), Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Legislation, State Operation of Project, Miscellaneous, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Legislation, State Operation of Project, Miscellaneous, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Interest Rate and Allocation, Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Legislation, Interest Rate and Allocation, Data from Authority, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Legislation, Interest Rate and Allocation, H.R. 1886, 1977, 2873, 2874, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Legislation, Interest Rate and Allocation, 81st Congress Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Legislation, Interest Rate and Allocation, Bills, Statements, Memos, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Drafts of Bills, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Conferences, Accession no. M0223 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Memoranda and Analyses - 1946, Accession no. M0223 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Memoranda Favoring Limitation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Memoranda Opposing Limitation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Legislation, Land Limitation Legislation, Interior Department Regulations, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Investigation of Reclamation Bureau, S. Res. 176, Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Investigation of Reclamation Bureau, Data from Authority, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Miscellaneous, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Southern California Edison Company, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Drafts - City of Los Angeles and Metropolitan Water District of Southern California Agreement, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Agreement of Metropolitan Water District of Southern California, Deferring Payments for Boulder Dam Energy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Boulder Canyon Dam Project - Calculation of Cost of Money to United States Government on Borrowings, Subsequent to 6/30/31, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Memoranda re: Nebraska vs. Wyoming, 6/11/45, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Verde River Irrigation and Power District - telegrams, articles, drafts, miscellaneous, Accession no. M0223 (Box 11, Folder 151)
- Series 2. General Subject files
  - Subseries 1. California Water Project
    - Construction of the Los Angeles Aqueduct - Final Report, 1916, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Report o the Feasibility of Irrigating the Palo Verde Mesa and the Chucawalla Valley, Riverside County, California,1/1/17, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Water - Where It Comes From... How It Reaches Your Faucet,6/46, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - King's River Project Cost Allocations, 1946, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Telegram, 2/18/47, A. J. Elliot re: Pine Flat Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - TL carbon, 2/17/47, Harry Trurn~n to Speaker, House of Representatives re: reclamation policies and report, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - TL carbon, 2/17/47, Harry Truman to Secretary of War re: King's River Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - TL carbon, 1/31/47, Robert P. Patterson to Harry Truman re: report on division of costs for King's River Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - TL carbon, 7/5/47, Edward Hyatt to Richard L. Boke re: memos on "Yolo-Solano Development of the Comprehensive Plan for Central Valley Basin, California" - comments, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - TLS, 2/7/57, John R. Teerink to T. Newman, W. S. Schulz and H.0. Banks re: transmittal of report on studies to integrate San Luis Unit and Feather River Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Report, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Presentation on Solano Project, Monticello Dam, by the Solano County Water Council, 4/48, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - TL carbon, 4/14/52, Michael W. Strauss to Secretary of Interior re: transmittal of report on Sacramento Canals Unit, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - TL carbon, 4/14/52, Michael W. Strauss to Secretary of Interior re: transmittal of report on Trinity River Development, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - TL carbon, 8/4/55, W. A. Drexheimer to Secretary of Interior re: transmittal of report on San Luis Unit, San Joaquin Division, Central Valley Project., Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - TL copy, 12/31/55, J. R. Kiely to Howard J. Williams re: transmittal of "Engineering Economic and Financial Aspects of the Feather River Project," with summary and recommendations, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - The Next 15 Years, 1955 - 1970 (1955), Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - TL mimeo, 8/1/56, Freda Seaton to the President re: transmittal of report on San Luis Unit, West San Joaquin Division, Central Valley Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Governor's Committee on Water, 11/19/56, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - TL mimeo, 12/17/56, Freda Seaton to Sam Rayburn re: transmittal of report on San Luis Unit, West San Joaquin Division, Central Valley Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Economic Conside~ations in the Formulation and Repayment of California Waèer Plan Projects, 3/58, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - TL mimeo, 4/28/58, Harvey 0. Banks to Northcutt Ely re: transmittal of Bulletin #58, Northeastern Counties Investigation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Interim Report of Financial Consultants to State of California Department of Water Resources on Financial Aspects of Program for State Water Resources Development System, 7/8/60, Accession no. M0223 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Interim Report - General Evaluation of the Proposed Program for Financing and Construction of the State Water Resources Development System of the State of California, Department of Water Resources, 11/60, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Report and Development Plan - Stanislaus River Basin Area for the Stanislaus River Basin Group, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - TL mimeo, 11/29/61, B. Abbott Goldberg to Frank J. Barry re: San Luis Unit, Central Valley Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - TL mimeo, 12/26/61, Solicitor to Secretary of the Department of the Interior re: agreement for San Luis Unit, Central Valley Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - TL mimeo,. 1~./16/53, Fred G. Aandahlto Secretary of Interior re: supplemental report on San Luis 'Valley Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - TL mimeo, 3/26/56, W. A. Dexheimer to Secretary of Interior re: supplemental report of San Luis Valley Project, with attached report, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Brief Review of Supplemental Report of Commissioner of Reclamation, Dated 3/26/56 on Rio Grande and Weminuche Pass Divisions, San Luis Valley Project, 9/17/56, Accession no. M0223 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - History of Central Valley Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2. Central Arizona Project
    - Report on the State of Arizona's Application for Preliminary Permit to Develop Power on the Colorado River at Bridge Canyon, 5/31/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Comparison of Diversion Routes - Central Arizona Project, 9/45, Accession no. M0223 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Comparison of Diversion Routes - Central Arizona Project; Appendices, 9/45, Accession no. M0223 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - ~ Report of Feasibility - Bridge Canyon Route and Parker Route - Comparison of Parker and Bridge Routes, 2/47, Accession no. M0223 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Presenting the Central Arizona Project to You, Accession no. M0223 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Report on Central Arizona Project - Project Planning Report 33-8b. 4-2, Accession no. M0223 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 81st Congress, 1st Session - H.D. 136 - Letter from the Secretary of the Interior Transmitting a Report and Findings on the Central Arizona Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Analyses of Water Supply - Proposed Central Arizona Project,3/49, Accession no. M0223 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - H.J. Res. 3 and Statements by Congressional members, Accession no. M0223 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Litigation Resolutions - 81st Congress, Accession no. M0223 (Box 16, Folder 1)